Testing Order Query...
Status: 200
Response: {'response': "You don't have any recent orders. If you've placed an order, it may not have been processed yet or the information might not be available in our system. Could you please provide me with your order number or more details about your order so I can try to assist you better?"}

Testing Product Query...
Status: 200
Product Test Failed: 'charmap' codec can't encode character '\u20b9' in position 105: character maps to <undefined>

Testing List All Orders Query...
Status: 200
Response: {'response': "You have no recent orders. Your order history is empty. If you've placed an order in the past, it may not be visible due to our system's data retention policies. If you need assistance with placing a new order for fresh groceries, I'd be happy to help."}

Testing JBL Product Query...
Status: 200
Response: {'response': "I'm sorry, but FreshCart only delivers fresh grocery products (Vegetables, Non-Veg, Fruits). We do not sell electronics or other items."}
